Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Publications Collection, 1887-2005 RL.00741
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Corporate Publications Series (Restricted), 1918-2005, 36 boxes
  - JWT Group Reports, 1981-1987
    - Financial Fact Book, 1983-1985, 6 folders (Box CJ1)
    - Financial Review, 1983 (Box CJ1)
    - Mission statement, 1981 (Box CJ1)
    - Morgan Stanley report, 1983 (Box CJ1)
    - Press kit, 1984, 1986 (Box CJ1)
    - Recent events, 1982, 6 folders (Box CJ2)
    - Recent press clippings regarding Robert Gray's complaint against JWT Group Inc., 1982 (Box CJ2)
    - Stock review and commentary, 1983-1985, 9 folders (Box CJ2)
  - Profile Books, 1970-1996
    The Worldwide and Domestic Profile Books were created by the International Intelligence Unit, in response to the number of requests for information and slides for use in New Business presentations. The Profile Books are fact books designed for employee reference. The information has been extracted from annual assessment plans. Each book is arranged alphabetically by country and includes such information as population statistics, office opening dates, billings, client product listings and rankings. Employees could purchase slides of the appropriate page from the most current Profile Book. Out of date slides were transferred to the JWWT Archives, some of which were retained in the Iconographic Collection: Slides.
    Organized into Domestic and Worldwide categories and arranged chronologically therein.
    - Domestic Profile Books, 1970-1974, 5 folders (Box CP1)
    - Worldwide Profile Books, 1973-1996
      - 1973-1979, 5 folders (Box CP1)
      - 1980-1986, 7 folders (Box CP2)
      - 1989-1991, 4 folders (Box CP3)
  - Profile Books, Restricted Materials (Closed to non-JWT users) 1992-1996
    - Worldwide Profile Books
      - 1992-1996, 4 folders (Box CP4)
  - Telephone Directories, 1953-2005
    Organized into Domestic and International categories, and arranged alphabetically by office, therein chronologically.
    - Domestic Offices
      - Chicago Office (Box CT1)
        - 1974-2002 (Folders for 1992-2002 removed to Domestic Offices, Restricted Materials, box CT4), 6 folders (Box CT1)
      - Detroit Office
        - 1983-1999 (Folder for 1992-1999 removed to Domestic Offices, Restricted Materials, box CT4) (Box CT1)
      - New York Office
        - 1953-1957 (Box CT1)
        - 1965-1984, 8 folders (Box CT2)
        - 1985-2001 (Folders for 1992-2001 removed to Domestic Offices, Restricted Materials, boxes CT4-CT5), 6 folders (Box CT3)
    - Domestic Offices, Restricted Materials (Closed to non-JWT users), 1992-2002
      - Chicago Office, 1992-2002, 10 folders (Box CT4)
      - Detroit Office, 1992-1999 (Box CT4)
      - New York Office
        - 1992-1998, 3 folders (Box CT4)
        - 1999-2001 (Box CT5)
    - International and Worldwide Offices, Restricted Materials, (Closed to non-JWT users), 1995-2005 and undated
      - Europe, undated (Box CT5)
      - Latin America, 2001 (Box CT5)
      - London Office, 2000-2001, 2005, 2 folders (Box CT5)
      - Mindshare, 2001 (Box CT5)
      - Worldwide Board of Directors, undated (Box CT5)
      - Worldwide directory, 2003 (Box CT5)
      - Worldwide Partners Council, 1995 (Box CT5)
  - Worldwide Office Fact Books, Restricted Materials (Closed to non-JWT users) 1994-2004
    Arranged chronologically.
    - 1994-2004, 9 folders (Box CW1)
- Domestic Publications Series (Restricted), 1887-2005 and undated, 32 boxes
  Organized into four subseries--Correspondence Relating to Publications, General Publications, Interurbia, and Individual Offices Publications. General Publications are arranged chronologically, and alphabetically by title therein. Other subseries are arranged alphabetically.
  - Correspondence Relating to Publications, 1945-1995
    - General, 1960-1964 (Box DC1)
    - [ Eyes on Thompson, 1993 (Removed to Correspondence, Restricted Materials, box DC2)] (Box DC1)
    - [ Innovative Ideas, 1995 (Removed to Correspondence, Restricted Materials, box DC2)] (Box DC1)
    - Interurbia, 1957-1962, 1969, 1978 (Box DC1)
    - JWT Manual, 1945 (Box DC1)
    - Population and its Distribution, 1928, 1931, 1961-1976, 5 folders (Box DC1)
    - Primer for Post-War Prosperity, 1937-1946 (Box DC1)
    - Some Things We Learned..., 1946-1951 (Box DC1)
  - Correspondence, Restricted Materials (Closed to non-JWT users), 1993, 1995
    - Eyes on Thompson, 1993 (Box DC2)
    - Innovative Ideas, 1995 (Box DC2)
  - General Publications, 1887-2005 and undated
    Publications that are not specific to a single office, though many were published by the New York office. Arranged chronologically and alphabetically therein.
    - 1887
      - Catalogue of Magazines (Box DG1)
      - Medical Journals (Box DG1)
      - Red Ear (Box DG1)
      - Religious Press (Box DG1)
    - 1889
      - Advertising in America (Box DG1)
      - Catalogue of Magazines (Box DG1)
      - Direct Acting High Pressure (Box DG2)
      - Thompson's Battery of Magazines (Box DG2)
    - 1890
      - Thompson's Battery of Magazines (Box DG2)
      - Thompson's Pocket Speller (Box DG2)
    - 1891
      - Catalogue of Magazines (Box DG2)
    - 1893
      - Catalogue of Magazines (Box DG2)
    - 1895
      - J. Walter Thompson Co. Advertising (Box DG3)
    - 1896
      - Thompson's Pocket Speller (Box DG3)
    - 1897
      - J. Walter Thompson Co. Advertising (Box DG3)
    - 1899
      - J. Walter Thompson Co. Advertising (Box DG3)
      - Red Book/J. Walter Thompson Co. Advertising (Box DG3a)
    - 1900
      - Thompson Red Book on Advertising (Box DG3a)
    - 1901-1902
      - J. Walter Thompson Co. Advertising, 3 folders (Box DG3a)
    - 1904-1905
      - J. Walter Thompson Company Advertising, 1904-1905 (Box DG4)
      - Thompson Blue Book on Advertising (Box DG4)
    - 1905
      - Where Good Advertising is the Constant Product (Box DG4)
    - 1906
      - J. Walter Thompson Co. Advertising (Box DG4)
    - 1906-1907
      - J. Walter Thompson Company Advertising, 1906-1907 (Box DG4)
      - Thompson Blue Book on Advertising (Box DG5)
    - 1907
      - Sermons on Advertising (Box DG5)
    - 1909
      - Advertising as a Selling Force (Box DG5)
      - JWT Book (Box DG5)
      - JWT Book, 1909 (Box DG6)
    - 1909-1910
      - Thompson Blue Book on Advertising (Box DG6)
      - J. Walter Thompson Co. Advertising (missing) (Box DG6)
    - 1910
      - Friendly Talks to Managers (Box DG6a)
    - 1911
      - 1910 Census Shows that... (Box DG6a)
      - Things to Know about Trade-Marks (Box DG6a)
    - 1911-1912
      - Thompson Blue Book on Advertising (Box DG6a)
    - 1912
      - Population and its Distribution (Box DG6a)
      - Population and its Distribution, 1912 (Box DG7)
    - 1913
      - Cutthroat Competition (Box DG7)
    - 1915
      - Are You a Guesswork Advertiser? (Box DG7)
    - 1917
      - What Magazine Advertising is Accomplishing (Box DG7)
    - 1918
      - Population and its Distribution (Box DG7)
    - 1919
      - How Advertising Helps Salesmen (Box DG7)
    - 1920
      - Photo Engraving Processes (Box DG7)
      - Population and its Distribution (Box DG8)
    - 1921
      - How to Break Down Resistance to Life Insurance (Box DG8)
      - Individual Effort Has Had Its Day (Box DG8)
      - Present Economic Conditions (Box DG8)
    - 1922
      - Prize Competition (Box DG8)
    - 1923
      - Gigantic Industry That Needs The Help of Advertising (Box DG8)
    - 1924
      - Population Handbook of Great Britain and Ireland (Box DG8)
      - What Do These Changes Mean? (Box DG8)
    - 1925
      - Purchasing Power of the Consumer (Box DG8)
    - 1926
      - Markets Are Made of People (Box DG8)
      - Population and its Distribution (Box DG8)
    - 1927
      - Retail Shopping Areas (Box DG9)
    - 1928
      - Selling at Home (Box DG9)
    - 1929
      - How I Selected an Advertising Agency (Box DG9)
    - 1930
      - Press in Its Relation to Public Opinion and Government (Box DG9)
      - Selling Abroad (Box DG9)
      - Treasurer, the Stockholder and the Customer (Box DG9)
      - Where They Live (Box DG9)
    - 1931
      - Economics of Advertising (Box DG9)
      - Population and its Distribution (Box DG9)
    - 1933
      - 25 Leading Advertising Agencies (Box DG9)
      - [ Competition under NRA (Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV1)] (Box DG9)
      - Merchant, Banker, Doctor (Box DG9)
      - Paper-Money Inflation in France: Where It Came from, What It Brought and How It Ended (Box DG9)
    - 1934
      - $5 Billion Sales Opportunity Knocking at the Door of Business (Box DG9)
      - Securities Exchange Act of 1934 (Box DG9)
    - 1935
      - Influencing the Mind of Another (Box DG10)
      - Problem and Opportunity for Milk in California (Box DG10)
    - 1936
      - Brookings Primer of Progress Illustrated (Box DG10)
    - 1937
      - Comment Vendre (Box DG10)
      - Merchandising of Food Products by Industry Co-Operatives (Box DG10)
    - 1938
      - Plea for Education (Box DG10)
    - 1939
      - Brookings Primer of Progress Illustrated (Box DG10)
      - Primer of Capitalism Illustrated (Box DG10)
    - 1940
      - [ Development and Application of Ideas in Advertising (Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV1)] (Box DG10)
      - More Jobs than Men (Box DG10)
    - 1941
      - Population and its Distribution (Box DG10)
    - 1945
      - Population and Purchasing Power (Box DG10)
      - Primer for Post-War Prosperity (Box DG10)
      - Review of Recent Advertising Aiding the War Effort (Box DG10)
    - 1946
      - Does Distribution Cost Too Much? (Box DG10)
      - World Markets for U.S. Exports (Box DG10)
    - 1947
      - Plant City Advertising (Box DG10)
    - 1948
      - Farm Market (Box DG11)
      - Market Potentials (Box DG11)
    - 1949
      - Consumer Purchasing Power (Box DG11)
      - Distribution (Box DG11)
      - Facts and the Gaining of Acceptance of Them (Box DG11)
      - Photo Engraving (Box DG11)
      - Plant City Advertising (Box DG11)
      - Some Advertising Responsibilities in a Dynamic Society (Box DG11)
    - 1950
      - JWT Consumer Purchase Panel (Box DG11)
      - Marketing Opportunities (Box DG11)
      - USA Market for Overseas Goods (Box DG11)
      - West Coast's Marketing Opportunities (Box DG11)
    - 1951
      - Cream of Your Market (Box DG11)
      - Direct Mail: Two Mediums Not One (Box DG11)
      - How to Step Up Production and Save Manpower Too! (Box DG11)
      - Marketing in a Defense Economy (Box DG11)
      - Population and its Distribution (Box DG11)
    - 1952
      - Wine Consumer Survey (Box DG12)
    - 1953
      - Ford Story (Box DG12)
      - Hidden Expansion Pressures in Our Economy (Box DG12)
      - J. Walter Thompson Co. International Organization (Box DG12)
      - Merchandising Case History: Shell Premium With TCP (Box DG12)
      - Today's TV Market (Box DG12)
    - 1953-1954
      - Where the TV Sets Are, 4 folders (Box DG12)
    - 1954
      - Huge New Markets (Box DG12)
      - [ Successful Examples of Mass Education by Clients of J. Walter Thompson Co. (Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV1)] (Box DG12)
    - 1954-1955
      - Some Things We Have Learned (Box DG12)
    - 1955
      - Consumer Market in the American Economy (Box DG12)
      - Huge New Markets (Box DG12)
      - Increasing the Knowledge Available to Management for Advertising Policy Decisions (Box DG12)
      - JWT TV Workshop (Box DG12)
      - Let's Try for That Extra 10% (Box DG12)
      - USA Market for Overseas Goods (Box DG12)
    - 1956
      - Guide for Secretaries (Box DG12)
      - Index for Travel and Transportation Merchandising Library (Box DG12)
      - J. Walter Thompson Consumer Purchase Panel (Box DG13)
      - Japanese Market (Box DG13)
      - Latin American Markets (Box DG13)
      - Philippine Market (Box DG13)
      - Portuguese Market (Box DG13)
      - Technique for Producing Ideas/James Webb Young, Japanese edition (Box DG13)
      - TV Terminology (Box DG13)
      - TV/Radio Schedule (Box DG13)
    - 1957
      - Dictionary of Advertising Terms (Box DG13)
      - Facts You Will Want to Know about the J. Walter Thompson Co. (Box DG13)
      - Peruvian Market (Box DG13)
      - Plan for the Promotion of American Travel in Thailand (Box DG13)
      - Western European Markets (Box DG13)
    - 1958
      - Advertising as a Career for Women (Box DG14)
      - Alaskan Market (Box DG14)
      - American Drug Store, a Qualitative Study (Box DG14)
      - Canadian Markets (Box DG14)
      - J. Walter Thompson Co. Style Manual (Box DG14)
      - Manual of TV Basics, 2 folders (Box DG14)
      - New Era in Ford Retailing (Box DG14)
    - 1959
      - Advertising: a Career for Exceptional Men (Box DG14)
      - Australian Market (Box DG14)
      - Happily, So Many of Our Needs Are Filled by Products Promoted Through J. Walter Thompson Co. (Box DG14)
      - Indian Market (Box DG14)
      - Regional and Split-Run Magazine Availabilities (Box DG14)
      - Report on the Role of Radio in the Lives of American Housewives (Box DG14)
      - Testing Television Commercials (Box DG14)
    - 1960
      - Advertising: a Career for Exceptional Men (Box DG14)
      - Changes Affecting Policy Control in World-Wide Business (Box DG14)
      - Hawaiian Market (Box DG14)
      - Radio: an Individual's Medium (Box DG15)
      - Ryukyuan Market (Box DG15)
      - South African Market (Box DG15)
      - Tips on Type (Box DG15)
    - 1961
      - Cream of Your Market (Box DG15)
      - [ Introducing the J. Walter Thompson Company to Pittsburgh (Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV1)] (Box DG15)
      - New Revolution in Distribution (Box DG15)
      - Population and its Distribution (Box DG15)
      - Television in Latin America (Box DG15)
      - Tourism Research in Japan (Box DG15)
    - 1961-1962
      - Advertising: a Career for Exceptional Men (Box DG15)
    - 1962
      - Are We Shackling Economic Growth by Overlooking the Consumer? (Box DG15)
      - Results of a Survey for the Market for Travel to the U.S. in Japan (Box DG15)
    - 1963
      - Advertising: a Career for Women (Box DG15)
      - Facts You Will Want to Know about the J. Walter Thompson Co. (Box DG15)
      - Lord and Thomas Creeds (Box DG15)
      - Mexican Market (Box DG16)
    - 1964
      - Advertising Workshop: Dehydrated Tomato Juice (Box DG16)
      - Description of Artwork Commissioned by JWT (Box DG16)
      - [ Lidov Mural (Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV1)] (Box DG16)
      - One World of Sam Meek (Box DG16)
      - World of Demand (Box DG16)
    - 1965
      - International Standard of Living Comparison (Box DG16)
      - JWT Information Center (Box DG16)
      - JWT International Offices (Box DG16)
      - United States Stamps (Box DG16)
    - 1965-1966
      - Accelerated Opportunities in Advertising Account Management (Box DG16)
    - 1966
      - Advertising Gold Medal Awards (Box DG16)
      - Change and Challenge (Box DG16)
      - Guide to Print Media (Box DG16)
      - [ Inside This Booklet You'll Find 8 Ads... (Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV1)] (Box DG16)
      - Samuel Yellin Cellini Wrought Iron (Box DG16)
    - 1967
      - Career Opportunities in Advertising (Box DG16)
      - World Business (Box DG16)
    - 1968
      - Is JWT the Company for You? (Box DG16)
      - Isn't the Consumer the Real Key to Continued Economic Growth? (Box DG16)
      - JWT Europe (Box DG16)
    - 1969
      - Advanced Opportunities in Advertising Account Management (Box DG17)
      - Advertising and the Nationalised Industries (Box DG17)
      - Communications Forum Papers (incomplete set) (Box DG17)
    - 1970
      - Facts about JWT (Box DG17)
      - Print Media Information (Box DG17)
    - 1971
      - Case for the Full-Service Agency (Box DG17)
      - Does Advertising Manipulate Consumer Behavior? (Box DG17)
      - Glossary of Common Terms Used in Media Audience Measurement Research (Box DG17)
      - J. Walter Thompson Company World (Box DG17)
      - Media Information: Europe (Box DG17)
    - 1971-1972
      - Media Information (Box DG17)
    - 1972
      - Account Management Development Program (Box DG17)
      - Advertising: Manipulation or Persuasion? (Box DG17)
      - Humor: Its Serious Side (Box DG17)
      - Spot Buying at J. Walter Thompson (Box DG17)
      - Statement to the JWT-Japan Creative Staff/Wilson Siebert (Box DG17)
      - Trouble at Credibility Gap (Box DG17)
    - 1972-1973
      - Media Information (Box DG17)
    - 1973
      - Affiliated Companies (Box DG17)
      - Hospital, Surgical, and Major Medical Benefits (Box DG17)
      - Profit-Sharing and You (Box DG17)
    - 1974
      - Consumer in Crisis (Box DG17)
      - How to Keep Your Ads Out of Court (Box DG17)
      - Moving Target (Box DG17)
      - Review for Lever Brothers Company of the Independent Buying and/or Barter Services and JWT's Buying and Barter Service (Box DG17)
      - "We are Ready to Meet Change with Change" (Box DG17)
    - 1974-1975
      - Media Information (Box DG17)
    - 1975
      - Advanced Opportunities in Advertising Account Management (Box DG17)
      - Advertising in a Land of Less: Circa 1980 (Box DG17)
      - Change in the Marketplace (Box DG17)
      - Measuring the Audiences of Magazines (Box DG17)
      - One Advertiser's Response to Pollution, Inflation, Shortages and Whatever's Next (Box DG17)
      - Partners in the Marketing Revolution (Box DG17)
      - U.S. Commercial Television 1950-1975 (Box DG17)
    - 1976
      - Consumer Change in the mid-70s (Box DG18)
      - Consumer's New Reality (Box DG18)
      - Use and Abuse of Survey Research in Advertising Regulation (Box DG18)
    - 1977
      - American Consumer 1970-1990: Great Expectations (Box DG18)
      - Media Information (Box DG18)
      - Results of 1977 Business/Financial Press Survey (Box DG18)
      - Special Markets Group: The Black Consumer Market (Box DG18)
      - TV Violence: In the Eyes of the Beholders (Box DG18)
      - Understanding Buyer Behavior
        - 1. Basic Concepts (Box DG18)
        - 2. The Role of Information (Box DG18)
    - 1978
      - American Consumer 1970-1990: Moving Target (Box DG18)
      - JWT: Reputation and Reality (Box DG18)
      - Leadership at JWT (Box DG18)
      - Managing a JWT Office for Performance and Profit
        - 1. Clients, Client Relations and Client Service (Box DG18)
        - 2. Profit (Box DG18)
        - 3. People--A New York Office Perspective (Box DG18)
        - 4. Product and Profit--You Can't Have One Without the Other (Box DG18)
      - Memorandum Regarding Five Speeches Presented at the JWT Fifth World Management Meeting (Box DG18)
      - New Medium: Television in the 1980s (Box DG18)
      - Under New Management (Box DG18)
      - Understanding Buyer Behavior
        - 3. Brand Loyalty (Box DG18)
        - 4. Market Segmentation (Box DG18)
        - 5. Description or Explanation (Box DG18)
        - 6. Sales Out of Purchases (Box DG18)
        - 7. Penetration Growth (Box DG18)
        - 8. How Brands Differ (Box DG18)
      - What JWT Stands For (Box DG19)
      - Yes--But What Responses? (Box DG19)
    - 1979
      - Corporate Need to Communicate (Box DG19)
      - Understanding Buyer Behavior
        - 9. Multi-Brand Buying (Box DG19)
        - 11. The Dirichlet Model (Box DG19)
        - 12. The NBD/LSD Model (Box DG19)
        - 13. Models of Change (Box DG19)
    - circa 1970s
      - Blank in the Balance Sheet (Box DG19)
      - Dialog (Box DG19)
      - Tele Communications (Box DG19)
      - To Speak As Well As You Think (Box DG19)
    - 1980
      - [ Advertising Chicago Style: A Character All Its Own (Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV1)] (Box DG19)
      - Employee Relocation Handbook (Box DG19)
      - Under New Management (Box DG19)
      - Understanding Buyer Behavior
        - 15. Watching Television (Box DG19)
        - 16. How Advertising Works (Box DG19)
        - 17. How Sales Increase (Box DG19)
    - 1981
      - Advertiser Pocket Guide to Cable Communications (Box DG19)
      - Commercial Production Procedure Manual (Box DG19)
      - Many Worlds of S. Meek (Box DG19)
      - Mission Statement (Box DG19)
      - New Media Explorers (Box DG19)
      - Things We Have Learned About Employee Attitude Surveys (Box DG19)
    - 1982
      - Advertiser Pocket Guide to Cable Communications (Box DG19)
      - BUY (Brand Utility) Study (Box DG19)
      - It Was a Very Good Year (Box DG19)
    - 1983
      - 25th Anniversary Invitation (Box DG19)
      - Advertiser Pocket Guide to Cable Communications (Box DG19)
      - Cable Capsule (Box DG19)
      - Financial Fact Book (Box DG19)
      - JWT Career Opportunities (Box DG19)
      - JWT--Who Is It? (Box DG19)
      - National Creative Award (Box DG19)
      - Thomas Francis Sutton (Box DG19)
    - 1984
      - Advertiser Pocket Guide to Cable Communications (Box DG19)
      - Advertising (Box DG19)
      - Adweek Agency Report Card (Box DG19)
      - Cable Capsule (Box DG19)
      - Fifteen-Second Commercials: The Simple Truth (Box DG20)
      - J. Walter Thompson (Box DG20)
      - Management Performance and Evaluation (Box DG20)
      - National Creative Award (Box DG20)
      - Network Sports Essentials (Box DG20)
      - Pocket Guide to Media Terms and Media Math (Box DG20)
      - Selling from the Corporate Point of View (Box DG20)
      - Some Things We Have Learned About Managing a JWT Office (Box DG20)
      - [ Thompson (Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV1)] (Box DG20)
    - 1985
      - Cable Capsule (Box DG20)
      - Million Dollar Minute (Box DG20)
      - National Creative Award (Box DG20)
      - New American Consumer (Box DG20)
      - Womenscope (Box DG20)
      - Zap Proof (Box DG20)
    - 1985-1986
      - Primetime Television Schedule: The Essentials (Box DG20)
    - 1986
      - [ 1986 JWT/FDAF Meeting, August 10-13 (Removed to Oversize Materials, box OV1)] (Box DG20)
      - Advertiser Pocket Guide to Cable Communications (Box DG20)
      - Cable Capsule (Box DG20)
      - J. Walter :15: What Now? (Box DG20)
      - J. Walter Corporate (Box DG20)
      - J. Walter Guide (Box DG21)
      - J. Walter Thompson Yearbook (Box DG21)
      - U.S. Coffee Market (Box DG21)
      - What is Advertising? (Box DG21)
    - 1987
      - Advertising Planning Methods (Box DG21)
      - Creative Uprising (Box DG21)
      - Flippers: Changes in the Way Americans Watch TV (Box DG21)
      - JWT Yellow Pages (Box DG21)
      - Lexicon (Box DG21)
      - Management Reference Center Chronological Bibliography (Box DG21)
      - Thompson Way Handbook (Box DG21)
      - Tool Kit--Advertising Planning Methods (Box DG21)
      - Unconventional Wisdom (Box DG21)
      - Year One of the People Meter (Box DG21)
    - 1988
      - Cable Capsule (Box DG21)
      - Identification Standards Manual (Box DG21)
      - Surprise 1988 Forecast (Box DG21)
    - 1988-1989
      - TV Fact Book (Box DG21)
    - 1989
      - [ Advertising Leadership 1864-1989 (Removed to Oversize Materials box OV1)] (Box DG21)
      - American Lifestyles Presentation Tool Kit (Box DG21)
      - Graphic Standards Manual (Box DG21)
      - In Defense of Mass Media (Box DG21)
      - J. Walter Edge (Box DG22)
      - JWT World Identity Programs (Commodore, Graphic Standards Manual) (Box DG22)
      - Lifestages (Box DG22)
      - Media: The New Creative Frontier? (Box DG22)
      - People Buy Brands, Not Products (Box DG22)
      - Thompson Recruitment Advertising (Box DG22)
    - circa 1980s
      - Criteria for Selecting a Worldwide Agency (Box DG22)
      - Mission Statement (Box DG22)
      - Who-What-Why-When-Where of Public Relations (Box DG22)
    - 1990
      - J. Walter Thompson (Box DG22)
      - JWT Account Manager's Handbook (Box DG22)
      - JWT Guide to Research (Box DG22)